Simon Shishak

UI/UX Designer

+380976574964 skype: simon.shishak linkedin.com/in/shishak simon.shishak@gmail.com www.shishak.space



Summary

Over 10 years of extensive experience in Visual and UI/UX design Expertise in the latest version of Adobe Photoshop and Advanced level of hand coding HTML/CSS/JS. Understanding of current trends and design patterns.

Specialties: UI and UX Design, Visual and Graphic Design.

Experience

UI/UX Designer at Samsung Electronics

July 2011 - February 2015 (3 years 8 months)

- UX development (user goals identification, wireframes and user flow development);
- UI development (mockups visualization, graphical assets creation);
- UI/UX and GUI documents creation;
- Creating interactive UI prototypes;
- Mobile interface design;
- Mobile user experience design;
- Interaction design;
- Usability testing;
- Creating low and high fidelity mock-ups/prototypes;
- Standardization: creating product-specific guidelines, UI templates etc;
- Project promo materials creation (presentations and posters);

UI/UX Designer at Eqme Software

November 2010 - June 2011 (8 months)

- · User interface and user experience design;
- · Graphic design;
- Website front-end development;
- User analysis (creating personas, scenarios, user interviews etc.);
- Creating interactive UI prototypes;
- · Usability testing;
- Creating low and high fidelity mock-ups/prototypes;
- UX development (user goals identification, wireframes and user flow development);
- UI development (mockups visualization, graphical assets creation);

Web Designer at Nestandart Web Studio

December 2009 - November 2010 (1 years)

- · Website design;
- · Graphic design;
- Website front-end development;
- Website developing with popular CMS (Wordpress, Joomla);
- Development of design layouts of printed products;
- Development of corporate identity;
- · Prepress printing products;

Web Designer at Avistar Clinical Research Support

April 2007 - November 2008 (1 years 8 months)

- · Website design;
- Website front-end development;
- Development of design layouts of printed products;
- Development of corporate identity;

Web Designer at Zfort Group

March 2006 - June 2006 (4 months)

- · Website design;
- Website front-end development;
- Development of corporate identity;

Web Designer at Deluxe Web Studio

January 2005 - May 2005 (5 months)

- · Website design;
- · Graphic design;

Skills & Expertise

User Interface Design, User Experience Design, Graphic Design, Interaction Design Mobile Design, Icon Design, Web Development

Education

Kharkiv National Automobile and Highway University (KhNAHU) Ecology, 2000 - 2003

Languages

Ukraine (Native)
Russian (Native)
English (Intermediate)